Against all odds they went to hell and back.
The Siege of Firebase Gloria is a action, war film
directed by Brian Trenchard-Smith.
A Marine patrol stops at Firebase Gloria at the start of
the Tet Offensive during the Vietnam war.
With the firebase attacked, the patrol remains to help defend it.
Cpl. Joseph L. 'Nard' DiNardo, played by Wings Hauser.
Sgt. Maj. Bill Hafner / Narrator, played by R. Lee Ermey.
Cao Van, played by Robert Arevalo.
Capt. Kathy Flanagan, MD, played by Margaret Gerard.
Pvt. Murphy, played by Mark Neely.
Capt. A.J. 'Bugs' Moran, played by Gary Hershberger.
The Siege of Firebase Gloria is a 1989 Australian war film directed by
Brian Trenchard-Smith, starring Wings Hauser and R.
It was filmed in the Philippines.
The film explores themes of vietnam war, vietcong, embassy, siege, sergeant.